[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "5+7",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["12"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "10+27",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["37"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "22-14",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["8"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "19+32",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["51"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "18+9",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["27"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "4+17",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["21"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "16+5",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["21"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "2+16",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["18"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "9+21",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["30"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "27-13",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["14"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "22-7",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["15"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "77-16",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["61"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "33-11",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["22"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "54-26",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["28"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "12-7",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["5"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "2+3",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["5"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "12+8",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["20"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "82-12",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["70"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "52-17",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["35"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "miniGame": "middlesex",
    "question": "9-4",
    "type": "written",
    "options": [],
    "answer":  ["5"],
    "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "7+3",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["10"],
  "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "20/4",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["5"],
  "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "12+15",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["27"],
  "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "25-6",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["19"],
  "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "7*3",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["21"],
  "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "16/2",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["8"],
  "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "22+2",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["24"],
  "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "8+22",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["30"],
  "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "30-10",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["20"],
  "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "4*9",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["36"],
  "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "45/5",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["9"],
  "difficulty": 1
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "(8 + 12) - (5 - 2)",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["17"],
  "difficulty": 2
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "3 * 4 + 10 / 2",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["17"],
  "difficulty": 2
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "(16 / 2) * (3 + 1)",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["32"],
  "difficulty": 2
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "9 + 3 - 4 * 2",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["4"],
  "difficulty": 2
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "(7 * 2) - (36 / 4)",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["5"],
  "difficulty": 2
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "22 - (8 / 2) * 3 + 5",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["15"],
  "difficulty": 2
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "(25 + 5) / (15 - 10)",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["6"],
  "difficulty": 2
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "(18 - 3) * 2 / 3",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["10"],
  "difficulty": 2
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "(24 / 3) * 4 - 16",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["16"],
  "difficulty": 2
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "56 / 7 + 12 - 3",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["17"],
  "difficulty": 2
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "Derivative of: (3x^2)+2x-5",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["6x+2", "6x + 2", "6x + 2 "],
  "difficulty": 3
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "Derivative of: 4x^3",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["12x^2", "12x ^2", "12x2"],
  "difficulty": 3
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "Derivative of: (e^x)+3",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["e^x"],
  "difficulty": 3
  },
  {
  "id": 1,
  "miniGame": "middlesex",
  "question": "Derivative of: (4x^3)-(9x^2)+x",
  "type": "written",
  "options": [],
  "answer":  ["(12x^2)-18x+1"],
  "difficulty": 3
  }
]